gmodstore.com 2019-01-21

# Privacy Policy · gmodstore

This privacy policy governs the manner in which GmodStore collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the [https://www.gmodstore.com](https://www.gmodstore.com/) website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by GmodStore. 

#### Personal identification information

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. 

This Site uses the Steam Web APIs to retrieve data about users only when those users login using the Steam OpenID provider. The data we store from the Steam Web APIs include 64-bit Steam IDs, Steam Community names, and URLs to Steam Community avatar images. 

#### Non-personal identification information

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information. 

#### Web browser cookies

Our Site places small data files known as cookies on your computer to make the site work better for the User. These cookies aren't used to identify you personally but they can remember activities and preferences chosen by you and your browser. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. 

**Cookies that make our Site work**

Cookie name | Purpose | Cookie type  
---|---|---  
gmodstore_cookie2 | To persist Users session. | Persistent  
gmodstore_sessionid2 | Used to identify Users session. | Session  

#### How we use collected information

GmodStore may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

  * **To process payments:** We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. 
  * **To send periodic emails:** We may use the Users provided email address to send them information and updates pertaining to their order. 

#### How we protect your information

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, transaction history and data stored on our Site. 

#### Sharing your personal information

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above. 

#### Changes to this privacy policy

GmodStore has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site and revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications. 

#### Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes. 

#### Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [legal@gmodstore.com]()

**This document was last updated on May 7, 2018**
